export const television =  [
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "From%20what%20show%20is%20the%20character%20%22James%20Doakes%22%3F%20",
"correct_answer": "Dexter",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Marvel%27s%20Daredevil",
"Boardwalk%20Empire",
"The%20Walking%20Dead"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20the%20TV%20series%20%22Person%20of%20Interest%22%2C%20who%20plays%20the%20character%20%22Harold%20Finch%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Michael%20Emerson",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Jim%20Caviezel",
"Taraji%20P.%20Henson",
"Kevin%20Chapman"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20year%20did%20the%20television%20company%20BBC%20officially%20launch%20the%20channel%20BBC%20One%3F",
"correct_answer": "1936",
"incorrect_answers": [
"1948",
"1932",
"1955"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20the%20Doctor%20Who%20universe%2C%20how%20many%20times%20can%20a%20time%20lord%20normally%20regenerate%3F",
"correct_answer": "12",
"incorrect_answers": [
"11",
"13",
"15"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20track%20by%20%22Massive%20Attack%22%20is%20used%20for%20the%20theme%20of%20%22House%22%3F%20",
"correct_answer": "Teardrop",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Protection",
"Angel",
"Black%20Milk"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20title%20of%20The%20Allman%20Brothers%20Band%20instrumental%20used%20as%20the%20theme%20to%20the%20BBC%20motoring%20show%2C%20%27Top%20Gear%27%3F",
"correct_answer": "Jessica",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Angela",
"Erica",
"Sandra"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Who%20sang%20the%20theme%20song%20for%20the%20TV%20show%20%27Rawhide%27%3F",
"correct_answer": "Frankie%20Laine",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Guy%20Mitchell",
"%20Tennessee%20Ernie%20Ford",
"Slim%20Whitman"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20what%20year%20did%20%22The%20Big%20Bang%20Theory%22%20debut%20on%20CBS%3F",
"correct_answer": "2007",
"incorrect_answers": [
"2008",
"2006",
"2009"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20the%20original%20Doctor%20Who%20series%20%281963%29%2C%20fourth%20doctor%20Tom%20Baker%27s%20scarf%20was%20how%20long%3F",
"correct_answer": "7%20Meters",
"incorrect_answers": [
"10%20Meters",
"2%20Meters",
"5%20Meters"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20Autobot%20names%20in%20Michael%20Bay%27s%20movies%20was%20NOT%20a%20name%20for%20a%20Transformer%20in%20the%20original%201980%27s%20cartoon%3F",
"correct_answer": "Mudflap",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Skids",
"Sideswipe",
"Ratchet"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Who%20was%20the%20star%20of%20the%20TV%20series%20%2224%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Kiefer%20Sutherland",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Kevin%20Bacon",
"Hugh%20Laurie",
"Rob%20Lowe"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20Ross%27%20pet%20monkey%20on%20%22Friends%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Marcel",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Jojo",
"George",
"Champ"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20character%20does%20voice%20actress%20Tara%20Strong%20NOT%20voice%3F",
"correct_answer": "Bubbles%20%282016%29",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Twilight%20Sparkle",
"Timmy%20Turner",
"Harley%20Quinn"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20Breaking%20Bad%2C%20the%20initials%20W.W.%20refer%20to%20which%20of%20the%20following%3F",
"correct_answer": "Walter%20White",
"incorrect_answers": [
"William%20Wolf",
"Willy%20Wonka",
"Wally%20Walrus"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Who%20co-founded%20the%20YouTube%20Let%27s%20Play%20channel%20%22Game%20Grumps%22%20alongside%20Newgrounds%20animator%20Egoraptor%3F",
"correct_answer": "JonTron",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Pewdiepie",
"Tobuscus",
"Markiplier"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20Naruto%3A%20Shippuden%2C%20which%20of%20the%20following%20elements%20is%20a%20%22Kekkei%20T%C5%8Dta%3F%22",
"correct_answer": "Particle%20Style",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Any%20Doujutsu",
"Shadow%20Style",
"Ice%20Style"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Dee%20from%20%22It%27s%20Always%20Sunny%20in%20Philadelphia%22%20has%20dated%20all%20of%20the%20following%20guys%20EXCEPT",
"correct_answer": "Matthew%20%22Rickety%20Cricket%22%20Mara",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Colin%20the%20Thief",
"Ben%20the%20Soldier",
"Kevin%20Gallagher%20aka%20Lil%27%20Kevin"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20the%20Netflix%20show%2C%20Stranger%20Things%2C%20what%20song%20would%20Will%20sing%20to%20himself%20as%20he%20was%20missing%3F",
"correct_answer": "Should%20I%20Stay%20or%20Should%20I%20Go%3F",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Love%20Will%20Tear%20Us%20Apart",
"This%20Charming%20Man",
"Africa"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20television%20shows%20makes%20everyone%20look%20under%20their%20chair%3F",
"correct_answer": "Oprah",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Jimmy%20Fallon",
"Saturday%20Night%20Live",
"Larry%20Rubert"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20%22The%20Big%20Bang%20Theory%22%2C%20what%20is%20Howard%20Wolowitz%27s%20nickname%20in%20World%20of%20Warcraft%3F",
"correct_answer": "Wolowizard",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Sheldor",
"Rajesh",
"Priya"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20surname%20of%20the%20character%20Daryl%20in%20AMC%27s%20show%20The%20Walking%20Dead%3F",
"correct_answer": "Dixon",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Grimes",
"Dickinson",
"Dicketson"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "How%20long%20was%20Ken%20Jennings%27%20win%20streak%20on%20Jeopardy%3F",
"correct_answer": "74",
"incorrect_answers": [
"88",
"49",
"62"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20%22Flash%22%20and%20%22Arrow%22%20spinoff%20featuring%20a%20team%20of%20characters%20that%20have%20appeared%20on%20both%20shows%3F",
"correct_answer": "Legends%20of%20Tomorrow",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Heroes%20of%20Tomorrow",
"The%20Justice%20Society%20of%20America",
"The%20Justice%20Society"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20which%20year%20did%20the%20British%20television%20series%20%22The%20Bill%22%20end%3F",
"correct_answer": "2010",
"incorrect_answers": [
"2001",
"2007",
"2012"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20British%20writer%20wrote%20for%20both%20Doctor%20Who%20and%20Sherlock%3F",
"correct_answer": "Steven%20Moffatt",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Phil%20Ford",
"Russell%20T%20Davies",
"Toby%20Whithouse"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Who%20was%20the%20winner%20of%20the%202016%20WWE%20Royal%20Rumble%3F",
"correct_answer": "Triple%20H",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Roman%20Reigns",
"AJ%20Styles",
"Dean%20Ambrose"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20Meg%27s%20full%20name%20in%20%22Family%20Guy%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Megatron%20Griffin",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Who-Cares%20Griffin",
"Neil%20Griffin",
"Megan%20Griffin"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "How%20many%20seasons%20did%20the%20TV%20show%20%22Donkey%20Kong%20Country%22%20last%3F",
"correct_answer": "2",
"incorrect_answers": [
"1",
"4",
"5"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20the%20television%20show%20%22Lazy%20Town%22%2C%20who%20is%20the%20actor%20of%20Robbie%20Rotten%3F",
"correct_answer": "Stef%C3%A1n%20Stef%C3%A1nsson",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Adam%20Sandler",
"Magn%C3%BAs%20Scheving",
"Stephen%20Carl"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20following%20is%20rude%20and%20dishonorable%20by%20Klingon%20standards%3F",
"correct_answer": "Taking%20his%20D%27k%20tahg",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Insulting%20and%20laughing%20at%20him%20at%20the%20dinner%20table",
"Reaching%20over%20and%20taking%20his%20meal",
"Punching%20him%20and%20taking%20his%20ship%20station%20position"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20%22Star%20Trek%22%2C%20what%20is%20the%20Klingon%20death%20ritual%3F",
"correct_answer": "Look%20into%20sky%20and%20yell%20loudly%20in%20mourning.",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Kiss%20the%20jagged%20forehead%20before%20burial.",
"Shoot%20into%20space%20in%20a%20torpedo%20casing.",
"Split%20the%20deceased%27s%20earnings%20between%20bloodkin."
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20breed%20of%20dog%20is%20%22Scooby%20Doo%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Great%20Dane",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Pit%20bull",
"Boxer",
"Doberman%20Pinscher"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20episode%20of%20%22Mr.%20Bean%22%20saw%20him%20trying%20to%20prevent%20people%20from%20seeing%20him%20naked%3F",
"correct_answer": "Mr.%20Bean%20in%20Room%20426",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Mr.%20Bean%20Goes%20to%20Town",
"The%20Trouble%20with%20Mr.%20Bean",
"Back%20to%20School%20Mr.%20Bean"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Alan%20Reed%20is%20known%20for%20providing%20the%20voice%20of%20which%20character%3F",
"correct_answer": "Fred%20Flintstone",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Bugs%20Bunny",
"Fangface",
"G.I.%20Joe"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20was%20not%20an%20actor%2Factress%20on%20the%20American%20television%20show%20%22Saturday%20Night%20Live%22%20in%20Season%2042%3F",
"correct_answer": "Tina%20Fey",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Mikey%20Day",
"Kate%20McKinnon",
"Sasheer%20Zamata"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20Battlestar%20Galactica%20%282004%29%2C%20what%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20President%20of%20the%20Twelve%20Colonies%3F",
"correct_answer": "Laura%20Roslin",
"incorrect_answers": [
"William%20Adama",
"Tricia%20Helfer",
"Harry%20Stills"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20main%20antagonists%20in%20Battlestar%20Galactica%3F",
"correct_answer": "The%20Cylons",
"incorrect_answers": [
"The%20Collective",
"The%20Federation",
"The%20Rebels"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20%22The%20Simpsons%22%2C%20what%20is%20the%20real%20name%20of%20%22Comic%20Book%20Guy%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Jeff%20Albertson",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Comic%20Book%20Guy",
"Edward%20Stone",
"Jack%20Richardson"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20WWF%20wrestler%20had%20the%20nickname%20%22The%20Ayatollah%20of%20Rock%20%27N%27%20Rolla%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Chris%20Jericho",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Marty%20Jannetty",
"Scott%20Hall",
"Shawn%20Michaels"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "%22The%20A%20Team%22%20first%20aired%20in%20the%20USA%20and%20in%20the%20UK%20in%20what%20year%3F",
"correct_answer": "1983",
"incorrect_answers": [
"1981",
"1985",
"1987"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20boxing%20personality%20was%20one%20of%20the%20presenters%20in%20the%201999%20revival%20of%20It%27s%20a%20Knockout%3F",
"correct_answer": "Frank%20Bruno",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Henry%20Cooper",
"Muhammad%20Ali",
"Joe%20Fraiser"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Baron%20Silas%20Greenback%20is%20the%20arch%20nemesis%20of%20which%20cartoon%20hero%3F",
"correct_answer": "Danger%20Mouse",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Bananaman",
"SuperTed",
"Captain%20Star"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Cesar%20Romero%20played%20which%20iconic%20Batman%20villain%20from%20the%201960%27s%20TV%20show%3F",
"correct_answer": "The%20Joker",
"incorrect_answers": [
"The%20Penguin",
"The%20Riddler",
"Mr.%20Freeze"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20Game%20of%20Thrones%20what%20is%20the%20name%20of%20Jon%20Snow%27s%20sword%3F",
"correct_answer": "Longclaw",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Oathkeeper",
"Widow%27s%20Wail",
"Needle"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "The%20first%20half-hour%20CGI%20cartoon%2C%20ReBoot%2C%20aired%20on%20which%20year%3F",
"correct_answer": "1994",
"incorrect_answers": [
"1993",
"1998",
"1999"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20the%20Sci-Fi%20television%20show%20Doctor%20Who%2C%20who%20plays%20the%20Tenth%20Doctor%3F",
"correct_answer": "David%20Tennant",
"incorrect_answers": [
"William%20Hartnell",
"Peter%20Capaldi",
"Peter%20Davison"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20actor%20portrays%20Hogan%20%22Wash%22%20Washburne%20in%20the%20TV%20Show%20Firefly%3F",
"correct_answer": "Alan%20Tudyk",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Adam%20Baldwin",
"Nathan%20Fillion",
"Sean%20Maher"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20actor%20was%20not%20a%20major%20character%20in%20TV%20Show%20Freaks%20and%20Geeks%3F",
"correct_answer": "Jonah%20Hill",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Jason%20Segel",
"Seth%20Rogen",
"James%20Franco"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Out%20of%20the%203%20Tots%20in%20Tots%20TV%2C%20who%20speaks%20French%20in%20the%20UK%20Version%20and%20Spanish%20in%20the%20US%20Version%3F",
"correct_answer": "Tilly",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Tom",
"Tiny",
"None%20of%20the%20Above"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Television",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20race%20horse%20that%20Tony%20Soprano%20becomes%20attached%20to%3F",
"correct_answer": "Pie-O-My",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Man%20o%27%20war",
"Bada%20Bing",
"Honest%20Earnings"
]
}
]